CHANON EKONGKARN

JR. GAME DESIGNER / QA GAME TESTER

(+66) 61-336-2497 | nappdevdotx@gmail.com

portfolio.com

ABOUT ME

I've been a Game Designer for half a decade including my years studying game design at the university and about a year as a QA Game Tester. I love seeing players enjoying the fun of the mechanics and the experience I have made for them. My expertise have increase in many side of the design, development, and testing.

SKILLS | LANGUAGES

Level DesignUnreal EngineGame TestingThaiMechanic DesignReport writing and Test CaseDocumentationEnglish (second language)Unity3D Animating (Maya)Attention to Details

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MAGNOLIA QUALITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION LIMITED

May 2024 - Nov 2024

Jr. Game Designer/Developer

- Participated in <u>The Forestias Project</u> in creating a unique 3D experience for adult clients and integrated Al into the project in Unreal Engine 5.
- · Handled unexpected circumstances with a mature attitude and sought the best solution for the project.
- Communicated clearly and precisely any changes in the project plans.

CHILLCHAT CREATIVE Jul 2023 - Jan 2024

QA Game Tester

<u>Primorden</u>: Identified and resolved 50+ bugs in the game through rigorous testing and collaboration with game designers, resulting in a significant improvement in gameplay experience.

- Planned and organized test cases for the game project.
- Created a good experience for players ensuring their experience is at its peak.
- Helped support other teams throughout the project with the Art and Design side.

THE MONK GAMES Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

Game Designer

Contributed to the design of the **XRB Galaxy**, specifically focusing on designing game concessions and economics.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Science and Technology,
Thammasat University

IDD CDT International Program Game Art Design

Modern International School Bangkok

Highschool

Feb 2008 - July 2016

Aug 2019 - May 2022

Won Best of Sound Award and was Nominated for Best of Game Design

Team Rolling Bear

Won Best of Sound Award and was Nominated for Best of Game Design